What does Lootera have, big tree lever
Anwar has a strong hold
on the insurance sector and Anurag is
preparing to tell a big news related to insurance, Anurag
tell me what is the news and what weaknesses are there in the
general insurance sector, there is
news related to the general insurance sector and here the
listed companies of general insurance will see the pressure reducing,
it will be affected, such long and
New India Assurance, as we
know that in the second wave of Kuber, the
claims of general insurance companies had increased a lot, there was a lot of
pressure
regarding the clamp and after that, last year the
insurance regulator had gone to
launch a product, Corona, which used to offer
only Corona-related treatment at a
very low premium, so for
some time now, the companies had
stopped selling the Corona product in this way
and then such conditions were imposed in which those
products could not survive that they were incurring huge
losses, so now in this series, the
companies have
started increasing the pricing and they have got
approval for uprising revision there, the
increase in premium has been approved
and in this  It is also being said that it had been
more than a year, hence
approval was given to increase the premium, so it is
good news for general insurance companies,
remember the way scientists were not
able to increase the premium in the Corona Kavach product related to Corona, that is, they were
not able to revise the premium, so those who
increase the premium according to their calculations, according to
their natural power,
they are getting approval there and
similarly, as there is a possibility of a third wave
and if the demand for the third wave is
high, then the companies will be
able to sell the product at their increased premium, it is good news for the entire general insurance sector,
where they were not able to increase the
premium of the Corona-related product, so
they are
getting approval to increase the premium and its effect can
also be seen on their portfolio of other health insurance
because the way the Corona
product has been approved, then in future,
other health insurance products can
also get approval,
so absolutely, big news is visible today,
Anil ji, how to see this news, as Anurag was
saying that  If these products
related to Corona get approval for celebration, then in
future other products can also
get approval for celebration. How to
see the service, the big news is this,
all these insurance companies whose
results are coming bad, this is an
opportunity to buy all these shortcomings and tell me the reason for this, the
serials which go bad are because
their claims are big during Corona,
but this is once again a big clash,
its effect which will be seen in the future,
after filling the long player roots and now
people have understood that it is necessary to have Mediclaim and
Life Insurance, so this is the
biggest thing, the kind of expenses that will be incurred for Mediclaim
in this time, from that
people should understand that there should be a sufficient insurance
and this is a one-time loss
but there is a life long benefit for these companies
and in this the first thing is that
awareness is spreading among the people who want to become a businessman and
people have understood that we need to have all kinds
of insurance and there should be adequate
insurance, so this bad result will be for
you, in all these quarter jails, in this
you must have General Insurance, all the shortcomings, that is why
we like New India Assurance a lot,
meaning this  Circulation which you must have
in the hotel, all this can do
wonders in 1 year from here,
you must take the best in India and such Kumar
and your problem is Chittor, the first thing is
clear cut, the important business which will grow in the coming one or two years is
tremendous
water, water retention, see the quarterly
results, you have reached to give you a great investment opportunity for a decade,
secondly you should now insurance premiums have started
increasing and this is the
best solution for them, for the first time on insurance premium,
we will see that the consumer should
take insurance from the front, otherwise
insurance always has to be sold, it
cannot be bought, the benefit is that if you can still do it, then this will
reduce the pressure, so both of these
can do wonders and sugar stock is this,
friends, you can buy it easily this year or
you can also that
when any of the government insurance companies can be
privatized,
which one will be India,
it is not known if there will be any disaster, but if this happens from that,
then think about the returns that can come in English stocks,
you cannot even imagine,
I think this post office is the one place you should
focus on, New India Assurance
Look at the chart Rai di Apni and after that I will
give a reminder of the fundamental rights filled with violence both newly and is a but
look at the charts images bar and just
start your drive 1956, do a
little bit of it, very nice post,
play NICEM Indian celebrity can be found,
look at the questions and paste